A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Overseas Development (OD), South and Southeast Asia (SSEA), Burma Office Program Files FA585
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Supervised Credit -- General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11)
- Supervised Credit -- General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 11)
- Supervised Credit -- General Correspondence (1/2), 1961 January-July (Box 12)
- Supervised Credit -- General Correspondence (2/2), 1961 August-December (Box 12)
- Supervised Credit -- General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12)
- Terminal Reports, Burma Ford Foundation Advisors (Part I), 1958-1959 (Box 12)
- Terminal Reports, Burma Ford Foundation Advisors (Part II), 1959-1961 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- Program Actions, 1954-1957 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- Robert E. Knowlton, 1959-1960 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- U Tha Hto, 1956-1957 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- Daw Soe Myint, 1955 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- Daw Tin Tin Oo, 1957-1959 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- Robert Myat San, 1958-1960 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- U Thein Tun, 1959-1961 (Box 12)
- Travel and Study Awards -- U Nyunt We, 1957-1959 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- Program Actions, 1957-1960 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 12)
- Advisor on Vocational Technical Education -- General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12)